plus.im 2014-02-13

# 

PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated: 8/11/2010

INTRODUCTION

This policy covers SHAPE GmbH use of personal information that SHAPE collects when you use https://plus.im and related pages. 

UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

This policy may change without notice from time to time and we will post these changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience of using our software and services. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website.

You are not required to provide personally identifiable information to use Services. However, in order to take advantage of certain features you may need to provide some personally identifiable information.

We ask for personal information when you create Service account, subscribe to our updates/news newsletters and when you want to submit a question about our products/services to our customer support staff. The types of personal information that we may collect on these pages are: name, company name, title, e-mail address, IP address. 

STORAGE AND USE OF YOUR DATA

We store the account credentials for all accounts associated with your Service account (network service, user name/email, passwords, etc.). These account credentials are stored encrypted. You can always adjust the information you have provided. We can not manually decrypt and/or restore your passwords. We can just reset them by your request for you could re-enter them once again.

We also store some of the data that is uploaded by you when using Services, such as pictures, voice records, chat history and other files you send through Services, your own display picture, the display pictures of your contacts, customized status messages, etc. SHAPE will use this data for providing Services purposes only. Some of the data may be stored on our servers for a reasonable period of time (but will not be available to others).

When you visit this site your IP address is recorded. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to create statistical reports about usage. Your IP address is used to help identify you to gather broad demographic identification that will not be tied to your identity.

This site also uses "cookies", which are certain bits of information that are deposited on the hard drive of your computer when you visit this site and sent back to this site when you visit again. We use cookies to maintain session information and to keep track of the number of users accessing our site and the information they access. 

SHAPE maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. We will not sell, trade, rent or lease your personal information to others. We use your personal information to provide requested information and to keep you informed of SHAPE commercial products and services to help ensure that the information we provide to you is relevant to your specific needs. If you do not wish to continue receiving marketing information, you can always unsubscribe from our newsletter by clicking on the appropriate link at the bottom of newsletter. If permission is granted, user information may be used to send occasional emails containing offers from our partners. This will only ever be provided to users who have specifically given us permission to use their information in this way. SHAPE will never use your data for anything beyond the reason stated and the permissions you grant us.

We use e-mail addresses to send you the alerts, newsletters and software updates/news information you've requested, to answer the e-mail we receive and to communicate with you about our software.

HOW CAN I DELETE MY INFORMATION? 

SHAPE currently does not have a method for completely deleting user information from our database. However, deleting the cookie stored on your computer will cause you to be perceived as a new user with no known user data. You may also change a setting in your browser, instructing it not to accept cookies, but this could prevent you from receiving some SHAPE’ services.

FEEDBACK

Information collected from feedback is used internally (if the user is submitting feedback about the site or software). We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor it is used for any other purpose. 

THIRD PARTIES AND EXTERNAL LINKS

This site contains links to other sites. SHAPE is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external Web sites, even those with whom SHAPE has established special relationships.

SHAPE cannot and does not assume responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, safety, reliability, timeliness, innocuousness, or legality of anything said, written, posted, displayed or otherwise made available by third parties.

SHAPE can provide your data to third parties if it is obliged to do so pursuant to legal provisions, it is forced to do so as a result of a legal case and/or in the event that it regards it as necessary for the protection of its own rights.
